<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright 2017 Yan Zhenjie

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>

    <string-array name="activity_start_items">
        <item>0. The use of the most primitive</item>
        <item>1. Demo request agreement</item>
        <item>2. Request images</item>
        <item>3. Request Json(JsonObject, Array…)</item>
        <item>4. Push Json、XML body…</item>
        <item>5. Define request(JavaBean)</item>
        <item>6. Five caching strategies</item>
        <item>7. The response code 302/303 redirection</item>
        <item>8. File upload demo</item>
        <item>9. File download demo</item>
        <item>10. How to cancel the request</item>
        <item>11. A synchronous request</item>
        <item>12. Through a proxy server requests</item>
        <item>13. Https request</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_start_items_des">
        <item>The most basic method of use, if I don\'t want to use the Demo of encapsulation, want to encapsulate the original use of developers look here.</item>
        <item>Http request protocol,: GET, POST, PUT, HEAD, DELETE, PATCH, TRANCE…</item>
        <item>The use of ImageRequest, Supports multiple request protocol, can carry cookies, request header, parameters, file transfer, etc…</item>
        <item>With Android\'s built-in JSONObject parsing. FastJson, Gson, XML etc and if necessary. Please see the request object.</item>
        <item>Submit a Json, XMl, ByteArray containing, InputStream, custom inclusions, etc., custom ContentType.</item>
        <item>Use FastJson custom Request, usage and NoHttp own Request, but faster and easier.</item>
        <item>No cache request network, network failure only returning to cache, only request network, read only the cache, the Http standard protocol.</item>
        <item>The response code /303/307/301/302 redirection, supporting a single redirects, multistage nested redirection, disable redirection through interfaces, etc.</item>
        <item>Support large files, documents, pictures, such as Binary stream of upload, through the Binary interface, support schedule notice, cancel the upload, etc.</item>
        <item>Download demo file, file downloads, download breakpoint continuingly, pause downloads, etc., such as errors, progress to inform developers.</item>
        <item>Support Activity, linkage, Fragment lifecycle support to cancel multiple requests at the same time, support according to the sign to cancel specified request.</item>
        <item>In child threads with NoHttp directly access to the network, synchronous get as a result, developers can combine RxJava encapsulation own request frame.</item>
        <item>To the request set up proxy server address and port through a proxy server to access the network, such as through their computer bag and so on.</item>
        <item>SSL certificate, a self-signed certificate, certificate of exemption Https access, etc., using Java generic API SocketFactory Settings.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_method_item">
        <item>Request failed?</item>
        <item>1 GET</item>
        <item>2 POST</item>
        <item>3 PUT</item>
        <item>4 DELETE</item>
        <item>5 HEAD</item>
        <item>6 PATCH</item>
        <item>7 OPTIONS</item>
        <item>8 TRACE</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_method_item_des">
        <item>Why do the PATCH method request failed?</item>
        <item>The GET request method, parameters, request the specified page/interface information, and returns the entity body.</item>
        <item>The POST request method, submit the data to the specified resource (submission form, upload files).Data is included in the request body.</item>
        <item>The PUT request method, from the client send the data to the server to replace the specified content of the document.</item>
        <item>The DELETE request method, DELETE resources, request to the server, data, DELETE the specified resource.</item>
        <item>The HEAD request method, similar to a get request, but no specific content in the response returned, used to get the header.</item>
        <item>The PATCH request method, entity contains a table, the table shows that represented the URI of the difference between the original content.</item>
        <item>The OPTIONS request method, for server support HTTP request method, to check the performance of the server.</item>
        <item>The TRACE request method, the echo server receives the request, it is mainly used for testing or diagnosis.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_image_item">
        <item>GET</item>
        <item>POST</item>
        <item>PUT</item>
        <item>DELETE</item>
        <item>OPTIONS</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_cache_entrance">
        <item>DEFAULT.</item>
        <item>REQUEST_NETWORK_FAILED_READ_CACHE.</item>
        <item>NONE_CACHE_REQUEST_NETWORK</item>
        <item>ONLY_READ_CACHE</item>
        <item>ONLY_REQUEST_NETWORK</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_cache_entrance_des">
        <item>NoHttp default cache mode, strictly abide by the RFC2616 agreement.Such as response Http304, returns available cache.</item>
        <item>Request network after failing to return to the last successful data, if one had no request is successful, the request fails.</item>
        <item>First read the cache, if there is no cache to request network, request data cached after come back, can be directly read next time.</item>
        <item>Just read the cache, not to request network.No cache that failures, exception types: NotFoundCacheError.</item>
        <item>When only request network, the network will not add cache first, request return whether cache data with the Http protocol.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_cache_item">
        <item>Request String</item>
        <item>Request Image</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_rxjava_item">
        <item>Request String</item>
        <item>Request Image</item>
        <item>DefineRequest FastJson</item>
        <item>DefineRequest JavaBean</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_redirect_item">
        <item>Initiate the request, allowing the redirection</item>
        <item>Initiate the request, does not allow the redirection</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_upload_item">
        <item>Upload a single file</item>
        <item>Upload multiple files</item>
        <item>Upload a file List</item>
        <item>From the picture album to choose (case)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_download_item">
        <item>Downloading a single file</item>
        <item>To download multiple files</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_cancel_item">
        <item>With the Activity/fragments joint statement cycle.</item>
        <item>Specify a few requests to cancel the queue.</item>
        <item>Cancel all requests in the queue \ n (including) has been in the implementation.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="activity_https_item">
        <item>The Https certificate request</item>
        <item>Avoid the Https certificate request</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>